<?xml version="1.0"?>
<teaser>
	<item heading="About the conference" label="About" image="images/image_1.jpg" link="page_1.pdf">
	<![CDATA[The year 2011 marks the 13th event of the Annual Conference on World Wide Web Applications. The 2011 Conference will be hosted by the University of the Witwatersrand's Knowledge and Information Unit in Johannesburg from Wednesday 14th to Friday 16th September. 	
The Conference covers a wide variety of areas from e-Learning and web applications to software development and e-Commerce. ZA-WWW 2011 is about creating conversations around the web that could lead to new insights and developments in the field.]]>
	</item>
	<item heading="Corporate Sponsorship Opportunities" label="Corporate" image="images/image_2.jpg" link="page_2.pdf">
	<![CDATA[The 2011 ZA-WWW conference gives corporates the unique opportunity to gain a platform for your company or service. You'll be able to interact with prominent role players involved in various aspects of the WWW. This includes industry professionals, academics and students. Sponsorships are designed and tailored to suit your particular needs. You let us know what your interests are and how you would like to be involved and we'll get in touch to work out all the details.
	]]>
	</item>
	<item heading="Your WWW timeline" label="Timeline" image="images/image_3.jpg" link="https://elearn.wits.ac.za/elsi/index.php?module=elsiskin&action=timeline">
	<![CDATA[2011 marks two decades of the WWW, a history marked with seminal moments and individuals who have left an indelible mark. From the .com boom and web 2.0 to social networking and eCommerce the WWW has altered the way we work, interact, learn and conceive of the world. It has inspired devotion, anger, outrage, passion, progress, innovation and frustration. 
In this WWW timeline - we would like to invite those who have been seduced by the charms of the www, to tell us their tale, an anecdote to relate or a memory they wish they could expunge. We want your www stories for our web snapshots.
]]>
	</item>
	<item heading="Contact us for further details" label="Contact Us" image="images/image_4.jpg" link="page_4.pdf">
	<![CDATA[University of the Witwatersrand 
Knowledge and Information Management
eLearning Support and Innovation Unit
Private Bag 3, Wits, 2050

Tel: +27 11 717-7161
Fax: +27 11 717 7163
Email: tessa.murray@wits.ac.za / james.smurthwaite@wits.ac.za]]>
	</item>
</teaser>